look, you find me about the first amendment,
смотри находишь мне про первую поправку
yes, you deceived you twice with your mouth, the
ты да ты своим ртом обманул два раза
first time I immediately caught you in a lie. Yes,
первый раз я тебя сразу поймал на лжи Да
you,
ты
uh, spun, spun, admitted that you
ээ крутился крутился признался что ты да
paraphrased and I caught you in a
перефразировал и я тебя снова поймал на
lie again. Come on, you admit again that she didn’t
лжи Давай ты снова признаешь что она не
talk about revising the first  amendments
говорила про пересмотр первой поправки
yes And then we will look at the next
да А дальше будем разбирать следующий
one Hello Hello
та Здравствуйте Здравствуйте
You are
Вы
from St.
откуда
Petersburg I am originally from Rostov But I
санкт-петербург я родом из Ростова Но
live in California 18 years in 2 years
живу в Калифорнии 18 лет через 2 года
it will be before we were once in the
будет дто были когда-то в
USA on the 13th
США 13
where the
го где
state of Washington was strong what
были сил штат Вашингтон что там
they did there
делали прило
Ponya And now
Поня А сейчас
how much do you have to calculate I don’t have enough intelligence
сколько у вас посчитать не хватает ума
I’m
хватает я вас
checking you 24 correctly If in the thirteenth
проверяю 24 правильно Если в тринадцатом
13 then 24t 24 It’s just I
13 то 24т 24 Это же просто мне просто
was just interested I was just interested
было интересно Мне было интересно просто
or are you
или вы
crumpling I’m just wondering why
мнёте мне просто интересно зачем
ask such stupid questions it’s your
спрашивать такие тупые вопросы это у вас
stupid perception of these
тупое восприятие этих
questions learn  trust people Why
вопросов учитесь доверять людям Зачем
at least a little bit at least a little bit like that and where have
хоть чуть-чуть хоть чуть-чуть так а где
you seen
вы видели
people? If you don’t see people in people,
людей Если вы в людях не видите людей
wait I advise you to see a
подождите Я советую вам обратиться к
psychologist stop stop look at people And
психологу стоп стоп смотрите людям А
what does this have to do with you, you are a resident of St. Petersburg, a citizen of
причём тут вы вы житель Питера гражданин
the Russian Federation,
РФ
so are
так так
you in fga?  it turns out And it
вы сфга ли вам получается А вы
turns out interesting,
получается интересненько
yes Well, it’s better in a free country it’s there
да А ну лучше в свободной стране это там
g there g with us yes with us They ban these,
г там г у нас да у нас Запрещают этих
we’re doing it where the person who
мы проводим это там где человек который
chatted to the President of the United States recently announced his
болти в президента США недавно заявил о
desire to abolish the first
желании отменить первую
amendment Yes, who is it who said to abolish the
поправку Да кто это кто заявил отменить
first
первую
amendment  Hilary Wedge Yes, what does Hilary
поправку Хилари Клин Да а что Хилари
want she said
хочет она сказа
with
с
with regard to free speech well Well,
с касательно свобо слова хорошо Ну а
Hillary is who is
Хиллари она кто
now the nominee former nominee of the
сейчас выдвиженец бывший выдвиженец отм
party as president now a
партии в качестве президента сейчас
representative of the Democratic Party of the United States
представитель демократической партии США
Well, well Show me where she said there the
Так а ну Покажите где она говорила там
first amendment
первую поправку
abolish
отменить
show us no problem
покажите вищ нас без проблем
Let's not directly propose to abolish it.
Давайте она не прямо предлагала отменить
She proposed to reconsider freedom,
Она предлагала пересмотреть свободу
namely stop stop stop you in Russian Chita
именно стоп стоп стоп ты по-русски Чита
don't stop stop you said what did you say with
не стоп стоп ты сказал что ты сказал
your mouth so that she abolish the first
своим ртом чтобы она отменить первую
amendment she said I said that And
поправку сказала я те сказал о том что А
tell me the
скажи мне
proposal for how to censor the media is this  not
предложение как бы цензури СМИ это не
abolition again once again you said with your
отмена ещё раз ещё раз ты сказал своим
mouth to repeal the first amendment I those
ртом отменить первую поправку я те
Initially said that it is stop
Изначально сказал то что она се стоп ещё
look again if not you said to repeal the
раз смотри если нет ты сказал отменить
first amendment you just clearly said
первую поправку ты прям чётко сказал
Let's
Давай мы сейчас с этим
figure it out now Why are you look let's figure
разберёмся Зачем ты смотри давай
it out If you now  Yes, can’t you find
разберёмся Если ты сейчас Да не находишь
where she said to abolish the first
где она говорила отменить первую
amendment, you admit that you were wrong
поправку ты признаешь что ты был неправ
And then the next statement is your statement of
А дальше разм следующее тво утверждение
freedoms of the masses, information erased,
свобод массо информацию ераз она где-то
she stated somewhere, she said to abolish the first
заяв она заявила отменить первую
amendment, she did not literally say
поправку она не дословно сказала
to abolish the first amendment, she proposed to
отменить первую поправку она предложила
reconsider stop, you said that she
пересмотреть стоп ты сказал что она
she said to repeal the first amendment then
сказала отменить первую поправку тогда
say that you were wrong and a little mistaken, the
скажи что ты был неправ и немного ошибся
wording was different, come on, tell me
формулировка была другая давай скажи мне
media censorship again No, let us Now we’ll
цензура СМИ ещё раз Нет давай мы Сейчас
deal with the phrases because I will
разберёмся с фразам потому что я буду
catch you in your
ловить тебя на твоей
nonsense About the first amendment Yes,
брехнею Про первую поправку Да такого
she didn’t say that You admit it now  that
Она не говорила Ты сейчас признаёшь что
you were in this yes Or maybe you made a mistake
ты был в этом да Или ошибся может
by accident Yes and let’s look at the following what
случайно Да и разберём следующее что же
she said let’s revise consider the
она говорила давай пересмотр считай
revision she wanted to do that
пересмотр она считай хотела сделать что
revise the first amendment Find this
пересмотра первой поправки Найди вот
specifically let’s find this means that by this you
конкретно давай найди вот значит этим ты
admitted Yes that you had no right to repeal the
признал Да что ты был не право отменить
amendment Come on now  you find where she
поправку Давай теперь ты найди где она
said revision first by revision
говорила пересмотр первый по пересмотр
count let's find me now you and I will
считай давай найди мне сейчас мы с тобой
hire again a
найм ещё
second
раз секунду
[music]
[музыка]
in3 gave you platforms
in3 gave you platforms
onity Because they were thought to be
onity Because they were thought to be
Pass they shouldn't be judged For The
Pass they shouldn't be judged For The
Content that is But We know  that
Content that is But We know that
look look you you are already you for a minute you are
смотри смотри ты ты уже ты минуту ты
turning on something for a minute Yes, find me a
минуту что-то включаешь Да найди мне
specific phrase Yes,
конкретно фразу Да где она говорила про
where did she talk about revising the first amendment? Let's propose to control the media once again, let's do it again no, I'm you again Find me where she talked about the first
Найди мне где она говорила про первую
amendment  Let's say the first amendment, what's
поправку Давай первую поправку что там
written there? Come on No, let's look
написано у тебя давай Нет давай смотри
where she talked about the first amendment.
где она говорила про первую поправку
Come on, I told you. Find the phrase where she
Давай я тебе сказал Найди фразу где она
talked about the first amendment. Come on. No, I'll
говорила про первую поправку Давай Нет я
be clear with you. You'll now
тебя чётко буду ты сейчас снова
admit again that you were wrong and we'll
признаешь что ты был неправ и мы будем
look into your next one.  statement
разбирать следующее твоё утверждение
Come on, this is control There is no freedom Let's
Давай это контроль Свободы нет Давай ещё
look again, we'll look at it now Show me
раз смотри мы сейчас разберём Покажи мне
her phrase where she said about revising the
её фразу где она сказала про пересмотр
first
первой
amendment again Control what the first
поправки ещё раз Контрол чего первой
amendment looks again Find where she
поправки ещё раз смотри Найди где она
said About the first amendment, just
сказала Про первую поправку вот просто
any sentence about the first amendment
любое предложение про первую поправку
let's not give  I'm turning off the sound for you,
давай не давай я тебе отключаю звук
look, find me about the first amendment,
смотри находишь мне про первую поправку
yes, you deceived you twice with your mouth, the
ты да ты своим ртом обманул два раза
first time I immediately caught you in a lie. Yes,
первый раз я тебя сразу поймал на лжи Да
you were spinning, spinning, admitted that you were
ты крутился крутился признался что ты да
paraphrasing, and I caught you in a
перефразировал и я тебя снова поймал на
lie again. Let's admit again that she didn't
лжи Давай ты снова признаешь что она не
say anything.  about the revision of the first amendment,
говорила про пересмотр первой поправки
yes And then we will analyze the next
да А дальше будем разбирать следующий
thesis, let's look at the first amendment of the United States,
тезис давай смотри первая поправка США
Congress should not make
конгресс не должен издавать законов Уста
any laws. Mouth and again, look where she
какую-либо и ещё раз смотри где она
said, I know what the first
сказала я знаю как звучит первая
amendment of the Constitution sounds like. Yes, tell me where
поправка Конституции Да ты мне скажи где
she said, let's violate the first
она сказала давай нарушение первой
amendment  show me again where she said
поправки ещё раз покажи где она сказала
that the first amendment of the
что нужно пересмотреть первую поправку
United States needs to be revised or not where she said to revise
США или нет где она сказала пересмотреть
Show me where she said
Покажи где она сказала
revision I’m asking for the last time if
пересмотре Последний раз спрашиваю если
you don’t answer I’m telling you you’re going
ты не отвечаешь Я тебе объявляю ты идёшь
where she said About the first amendment
где она сказала Про первую поправку
the first amendments or not you’re still going Let’s
первые поправки или нет всё идёшь Давай
subscribe to  miy Telegram right now axis
подпишись на мий Telegram прям зараз ось
vin
вин
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through the skarg Orcs into your ban
загоняя нас через скарг Орки в твый бан
and even more videos I don’t show people
и дуже багато видео не показую людям
at all times I don’t show information about ST to that
вчасно не показуе информация про СТ тому
for that, for that shob mi Mali operational link
для того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
to write directly at once and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegra  okm vdeo ezh tezh tsikava and korisna
телегра окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and mi povinni z you trimati
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in togo chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава Украине пись